so you ever found yourself on wish
Amazon Aliexpress I don't know if you
can use Ollie Baba calm I'm pretty sure
you have to go through all the Express
I'm not sure on that one but you've
always been warned about these little
portable little cheap Chinese radios
that they sold am wondering if they're
any good well here's a review of the
mini speaker l 288 and I think there's
also one that's called the Lee wall or
something like that anyhow so anyhow on
the mini speaker the L 288 I want to say
first of all there's no Bluetooth
functionality on this one and there's no
aux input that that's a little
disappointing that it doesn't have an
aux input because it doesn't sound that
bad and in the back I'm not gonna try to
pull the battery out but it's one that
you'd find in like a Nokia phone which
is nice because they were chargeable
holds like I think it holds about six
hours of bet no and six hours about five
hours of just straight continuous play
off the radio and which it does have a
kind of ridiculously long antenna I
maybe I should stand further back I mean
like sort of fight with this intense
looks like an RC controller no oh yeah
okay let's turn the thing on not that
hard all you gotta do is hold there
little red power button and when you do
that it'll just automatically take you
into if you have an SD card on the
bottom of it it'll take you right into
playing some music it really don't sound
that bad for a little radio that I paid
12 bucks worth
you know let's pause that now you want
to go to m1 go to FM there's no I am on
this radio
but fm they've got it on my favorite
crappy eighty station which I'd like to
play the music off of that but I
probably get my video too struck down
anyhow let's just do that then let's
connect this thing actually has a unique
way in which you can change the radio
station I mean you could hit that and it
changes the channels which you can
program I still haven't bothered to do
that but you want to go to like let's
say I want to go to the cable radio
station you just put the numbers in and
it takes you right there pretty pretty
nice a neat little feature but let's
let's go but let's go back to the mp3
function it's also got a USB you can put
a flash drive on the thing now back got
some got some retro way of going on here
[Music]
it'll sound that bad however what if we
go to like some not that one well we'll
be going like one of my favourite songs
although that's not it this would be it
I'm not editing that out there's
probably fix my hair
[Music]
they really just doesn't sound that bad
I'm actually amazed at the microphone
this can actually pick it up with pretty
clarity I'm actually happy about that
it's also go pretty loud too
[Applause]
not really super loud I mean III had the
thing at work and when I had this little
thing at work and an antenna it's
sitting pretty close to me I could hear
just fine there but if you walked away
you couldn't hear it at all but this
little thing for like the twelve sixteen
dollars or whatever I paid for it I
bought it off a wish took it a while to
get here this one came with a battery
that's an important one you want him to
come with a battery get bit it's nice
now I have another one and I'm gonna do
a separate video on that dead that
didn't come with a battery but the one
out of this one works just fine in it I
actually like it a little bit more and
I'll explain why anyhow thank you for
watching this is a half-assed product
review of the L 288 mini speaker
hopefully it answers questions if you
wanted to purchase one
[Music]
look at the Maserati go